<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IMI Showtime</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/</link><description>Recent content on IMI Showtime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m3-intu/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m3-intu/features/</guid><description>Interactive Learning Content Intu incorporates interactive learning objects, providing users with the opportunity to actively engage with the content. This includes an animated, exploratory diagram that offers a guided view while also supporting full user control. In addition a practical implementation of the MVC Pattern enables students to better understand and explore relationships within the content. To ensure understanding and retention, Intu also features practical tasks for users to apply and test their newly acquired knowledge.</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m6-vamx/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m6-vamx/features/</guid><description>Features VamX Vamx is a editor tool that allows multiple sounds instances to be grouped and controlled by a single component.
The Editor component allows the user to import a sound file and manipulate various sound properties using different evaluation methods, such as custom graphs for complex sound manipulation. The various sound properties and their evaluation settings can be saved as presets and reused in other sound files.
The Editor allows importing regular audio files via the Unity-Editor</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m6-vamx/techstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m6-vamx/techstack/</guid><description>Tech Stack Within the Unity game engine, we developed the sound framework and built the VR test environment. It provided us with many build-in features for programming with sounds and was well suited for development with VR. The XR Interaction Toolkit offered us all the basic functions for interaction in VR. With the help of input events and haptic feedback, we were able to make the minigames more interesting and created a good gaming experience.</description></item><item><title>Download</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m6-vamx/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m6-vamx/process/</guid><description> Download You can download VamX and the games here.</description></item><item><title>Process</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m3-intu/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m3-intu/process/</guid><description>Requirement analysis During the initial phase of our project, we engaged in extensive brainstorming sessions to determine what features our learning application should provide. We came up with more than 70 ideas and requirements that we considered interesting and worthy to explore. During this phase, we gave special attention to identifying strengths and weaknesses of current learning platforms, and emphasized on finding potential new and innovative approaches. Following the brainstorming phase, we conducted several iterations of prioritization which helped us narrow down our focus.</description></item><item><title>Tech Stack</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m3-intu/techstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ss23/master/m3-intu/techstack/</guid><description>Concept &amp;amp; Design Miro
Miro was used for the initial brainstorming session, for concretizing the requirements and concept, and for the wireframes. It allowed the team to discuss and visualize ideas and record decisions.
Figma
Figma was used to create the UI component library, styleguide and final design of the user interface of intu.
Development React
React is a progressive JavaScript framework, leveraging its capabilities to build interactive user interfaces.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/contact/</guid><description>The IMIxShowtime is a showcase of the term-long practical projects in the International Media and Computing Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s and Master&amp;rsquo;s programs. It takes place every term on the Friday of the last week of lectures.</description></item><item><title>IMI-Showtime via Zoom</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/zoom-help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/zoom-help/</guid><description>1. Install or update Zoom If you do not have the Zoom client installed yet, you can get it here:
Windows | Other platforms
If you already have the client installed, please make sure it is up to date. 2. Join the Zoom session Simply follow this link: https://htw-berlin.zoom.us/j/97320821203
3. Switching rooms To switch from the main session into breakout rooms you first need to click on the „Breakout Rooms“ button (1) and then click „Join“ for the desired room (2) and confirm with „Yes“ (3).</description></item><item><title>Important Dates</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/dates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/dates/</guid><description>After Showtime is just before the next Showtime - upcoming events:</description></item><item><title>Imprint</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/imprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/imprint/</guid><description>Diese Seite präsentiert Praxisprojekte der Studiengänge Internationale Medieninformatik Bachelor und Internationale Medieninformatik Master der HTW Berlin und ergänzt diese Webseiten.
Redaktionelle Verantwortung und verantwortliche Ansprechperson Studiengangssprecher der Studiengänge Internationale Medieninformatik
Prof. Dr. Gefei Zhang
HTW Berlin, Fachbereich 4
Wilhelminenhofstr. 75A
12495 Berlin
gefei.zhang@htw-berlin.de
https://www.htw-berlin.de/impressum/
Telefon: +49 30 5019 - 3738
Urheberschutz und Nutzung Die Urheber räumen Ihnen ganz konkret das Nutzungsrecht ein, sich eine private Kopie für persönliche Zwecke anzufertigen. Nicht berechtigt sind Sie dagegen, die Materialien zu verändern und/oder weiter zu geben oder gar selbst zu veröffentlichen.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Es gilt die Datenschutzerklärung der HTW Berlin.
Diese Website verwendet keine Cookies und speichert keine Informationen, die über die üblichen Server-Logs der Webserver unter https://htw-berlin.de/ und https://github.com/ für https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/ und https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/staging/ hinausgehen.</description></item><item><title>Project Overview</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/archive/</guid><description>Complete Project Archive - under Construction:</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/projects/</guid><description>This term there are 5 bachelor&amp;rsquo;s and 5 master&amp;rsquo;s projects. To get an idea of the scope and characteristics of our projects, you may also want to visit the archive.</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://htw-imi-showtime.github.io/preview/schedule/</guid><description>There will be brief project presentations with a quick Q&amp;amp;A in the morning (very brief presentations, the odd times are real, we might even be a bit quicker than this) and a project fair in the afternoon.</description></item></channel></rss>